

PEDRO SASTRE

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth: 19/10/95 Nationality: Argentina Telephone: +34 645222050

E-Mail: pedro2000sastre@gmail.com Address: Distrito Centro, Málaga

Web portfolio: <u>www.pedro-sastre-2024.web.app</u> LinkedIn: <u>www.linkedin.com/in/pedro-sastre</u>

GitHub: github.com/psastre

PROFILE

Data analyst specialized in marketing, trained to inform effective business strategies and decisions, with experience in small businesses where I incorporated best practices such as direct and personal communication, adaptability and flexibility for a dynamic environment, and the ability to engage in a variety of different types of tasks and projects.

SKILLS AND LANGUAGES

-SQL -MySQL -Python -SQL Server

-Tableau -PHP -Power BI -HTML -Excel -CSS

-Google Sheet -Javascript

- Azure - Spanish: C2 Native

-Matplotlib -English: C1 -Pandas -Portuguese: B1

-Numpy

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. Data Analyst

Soluciones Hogar | 2022 - 2024 Intermediary between professionals and clients in home repair services.

-I led the market research and customer relationship analysis to implement a new internal software, web platform, and modernize communication channels. I focused on operational optimization and enhancing customer experience, particularly in email marketing. I supervised data collection, processing, and analysis for strategic insights. I collaborated with interdisciplinary teams and utilized tools such as Excel, SQL, Tableau, Python, and Azure for detailed analysis and report presentation.

Database administrator and backend developer for Startup

ScoutPro | january 2023 -december 2023

- Responsible for designing, implementing, maintaining, and managing databases to ensure efficiency and security. Tasks include planning database design with various types of relationships, optimizing performance, and implementing security measures. The main tools used are SQL (MySQL and Workbench) and PHP.

Marketing Data Analyst

Soluciones Hogar | 2020 - 2022 Intermediary between professionals and clients in home repair services.

-Responsible for collecting, cleaning, processing, exploring, analyzing, and communicating data related to email marketing campaigns and subscribers, as well as monthly statistics on order management and logistics. Additionally, provided assistance in utilizing best practices and communication with graphics in the finance area. Used tools such as Excel, Google Sheets, Tableau, SQL, and Python.

ACADEMIC TRAINING

My data analysis Blog to establish concepts www.medium.com/@pedro2000sastre

February 2024

Google Data Analytics Certificate

November 2023 - December 2023

Alex the analyst bootcamp Jenuary 2023 - July 2023

React bootcamp

january 2021 - february 2021 | Scrimba Academy

Full Stack Dev. Bootcamp

February 2018 - July 2018 | Digital House

Degree in Advertising

2015 - 2019 | UADE